(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ここはねぽらぼ学園！部活もクラスも違うけど、ねねたち同じ学生寮に住んでるんだ！
This is Nepolabo Academy! We're in different clubs and classes, but we all live in the same dorm!
ふざけて、笑って、時々喧嘩して。でも集まると、なんか落ち着く。
We goof around, laugh, and fight sometimes. But when we're together, it's just so relaxing.
今日も談話室、賑やか。誰かの声が聞こえるだけで、安心するんだよね。
The common room is lively again today. Just hearing someone's voice puts me at ease.
この場所で、私たちだけの学園生活を作るなんて、楽しそうでワクワクする。
Creating our very own school life in this place... sounds fun and exciting.
さあ、私たちの、輝く青春が、始まる！
Now, our shining youth begins!
ねぽらぼ学園 ☆5周年記念！！輝く学寮祭☆
Nepolabo Academy: 5th Anniversary!! The Radiant Dormitory Festival!
今日は学寮祭。生徒会が中心になって開催する、夏の一大イベント！
Today is the Dormitory Festival. It's a huge summer event organized primarily by the student council!
会長からの頼みで、急遽ねぽらぼで出し物を考えることになったんだけど――
At the student council president's request, we had to come up with a performance for Nepolabo at the last minute, but...
何も考えられてなーーーい!!!!
We haven't thought of anything at aaaall!!!!
やばいよ…気づいたら、もう当日だよ〜〜〜！
This is bad... before I knew it, the day had already arrived!
だから言ったじゃん、もっと早く集まって決めようって。
See, I told you! We should have gotten together and decided sooner.
いや〜、なんとかなるって思ってたんだけどな〜（笑）
Well, I thought it would just work itself out somehow (laughs).
うぅ…これはマズい…変なことやったら、会長になんて言われるか……
Ugh... this is not good. If we do something weird, what will the president say...?
よしっ、断ろう！！
Alright, let's just cancel!!
やめなー！！当日に断れるわけないでしょ！
Don't do that!! There's no way you can cancel on the day of!
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミちゃんならきっと許してくれるって♪
It's okay, it's okay. If it's Lamy-chan, she'll surely forgive us.
売れるって
It'll sell.
なんでラミィだけ泳がされる前提なのよっ！
Why am I the only one expected to go for a swim?!
……いや、まだ終わってない！ 学寮祭はお昼から……
...No, it's not over yet! The school festival is from noon...
ほんのちょっとだけ、まだ時間はある！
There's just a little bit of time left!
よし、とりあえず案を出してみよっか
Alright, let's try coming up with some ideas first.
学校の祭りといえば…… 焼きそば、じゃがバター、
When it comes to school festivals... Yakisoba, jaga-butter,
唐揚げ、クレープ、ポテト……
fried chicken, crepes, fries...
食べ物しかないじゃん！！
That's all just food!!
……でも今から仕込みはちょっと無理かもな……
...But it might be a bit too late to start prepping now...
まあできるとしたら 炎天下でカラカラな喉に染みわたる……
Well, if there's one thing we can do... For parched throats under the blazing sun,
ラミィ水！！
Lamy Water!!
これは売れるぞ～
This is gonna sell~
やめろぉぉぉ！！！
Stop it!!!
うっひょおぉぉ！しぼり出して～
Whoa! Squeeze it out~
バカなこと言ってないで！ もっと真面目に考えなさいって！
Stop talking nonsense! I'm telling you to think more seriously!
そんなに言うならラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
If you're going to say all that, what do you want to do, Lamy-chan?
ラミィ？そうだなぁ… やっぱり歌は歌いたいし、
Me? Well... I definitely want to sing,
バンドとか、かな？
so maybe a band or something?
ふつう
Standard.
ひねりがないな～い
No twists there~
……フッ
...Hmph.
こいつら……！
These guys...!
でもまあ、歌はいいかもね～
But well, singing might be good~
ショート動画用にいろいろな曲練習してるし、 その中から何かやってみる？
We've been practicing various songs for short videos, so should we try one of those?
じゃあねね、あれやりたい！！ 元気いっぱいの、ねねたちにピッタリなやつ！！
Then Nene wants to do that one!! The high-energy one that's perfect for us!!
あ～～～あれね！
Ah~~~ that one!
いいんじゃなーい！
That sounds good!
じゃ、とりあえずやってみますか！
Well then, let's give it a try for now!
キメマスター！！
Kimemaster!!
前人未到の未踏地だよなぁ
It's an unprecedented, unexplored land
そいゃー！
Soiya!
キメマスター！！ 作詞・作曲：田代智一
Kimemaster!! Lyrics/Composition: Tomokazu Tashiro
生まれ変わる一歩目は
The first step to being reborn is
一歩目が大事さ 恐れないで
The first step is important, don't be afraid
何度でも平気な顔で走り出して
Start running time and again with a straight face
行かなきゃ！上々の気分さ
Got to go! Feeling great
やってみたいことには欲張りだね
I'm greedy for things I want to try
欲張りごめんね 直さないよ
Sorry for being greedy, I won't change
何度でも未来を書き換えたくなるのさ
It makes me want to rewrite the future over and over
行かなきゃ！最高の仲間と
Got to go! With the best friends
星になろうよ 輝きたいよ
Let's become stars, I want to shine
今は今だけ
Now is only for now
後悔しないようにねっ
So you don't have any regrets!
さあおいで MONSTERS
Come on, MONSTERS
暴れちゃえ MONSTERS
Go wild, MONSTERS
こんなにも無敵 PIKA STARS!
So invincible, PIKA STARS!
夢が KIRA-KIRA
Dreams are KIRA-KIRA
無駄に KIRA-KIRA
Needlessly KIRA-KIRA
全進だ DOKA-DOKA!
Full speed ahead, DOKA-DOKA!
はわっ 通りまーす
Hawa, coming through
決まっちゃってる 全速モードでよいしょっしょ
It's decided, heave-ho in full speed mode
制限はね 無視だよ 何でもかんでもやっぱっぱ
Ignore the limits, just do everything
全力がいいよね 決め顔あり キメ顔あり
Going all out is best, showing a cool face, a determined face
最強 BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！
Strongest BIG BANG, aim for the future!
チェストー！
Chesto!
手とりあったるんたった 怖くはないよね
Holding hands, skipping along, it's not scary
夢の計速メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
The dream speed meter is about to max out
地球からやってきたボクらは
We who came from Earth
本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
Today as well, Go ahead! Go ahead!
踊られるまで？
Until we're made to dance?
…怒られても止まらないのです
...Even if we get scolded, we won't stop
騒がしくて ごめんなさーい！
Sorry for being so noisy!
全人類だい？
All humanity?
ボクらだい！
It's us!
いわゆる前人未到の未踏地だよなぁ
It's a so-called unprecedented, unexplored land
そいゃー！
Soiya!
ゆずらないないない休日も
Uncompromising holidays
百歩ゆずるなんて負けよ球団よ
Giving an inch is a loss, my team
ゴールへのロードは砂利と岩だらけで
The road to the goal is full of gravel and rocks
泣いても顔は “に・や・り”
Even if I cry, my face has a "grin"
そんな時 お空は遠く澄め
At such times, the sky is clear and distant
だってほらあきらめたくない事が
Because look, things I don't want to give up
進化して みんなを果ての果ての空へ
Evolve and take everyone to the farthest sky
連れ去るボクら地球な子
Taking them away, we children of Earth
憧れたんだ 星の光は
I yearned for it, the starlight
消えないときめき
A throb that never fades
心拍数上がりまくりっ
Heart rate rising like crazy
さあ跳んで MONSTERS
Come on, jump, MONSTERS
暴れちゃお MONSTERS
Let's go wild, MONSTERS
大胆で不敵 PIKA STARS!
Bold and fearless, PIKA STARS!
夢が KIRA-KIRA
Dreams are KIRA-KIRA
上昇中 つまり好調中
Rising, in other words, in good shape
あ サビきまーす
Ah, here comes the chorus
多分勝利は 決まっちゃってる！
Victory is probably decided!
いいとこだったのに！
It was a good part!
バンドじゃないからせっせっせ カッコつけなければ
Since it's not a band, we've got to pose
バンドじゃないからよいよいよい カッコがつくのだよ
Since it's not a band, it looks cool
バカ騒ぎ
Raucous party
やんちゃ騒ぎ
Naughty party
やったもん勝ち 狙っちゃえ未来！
The winner takes all, aim for the future!
チェストー！
Chesto!
銀河のどっかの頂点に旗を立てるまで
Until we plant a flag at the peak of somewhere in the galaxy
ニューなレコードの道標は続くんだってば
The record-breaking trail continues, I tell you
地球からやってきたボクらよ
We who came from Earth
やりまくれ Go ahead! Go ahead!
Do it all, Go ahead! Go ahead!
Hey!
さあ次の星へ！
Come on, to the next star!
一歩が百歩の始まり
One step is the beginning of a hundred
だから行こうよ すぐに行こうよ
So let's go, let's go right away
無理は道理よりも強引だなー
Impossible is more forceful than reason
瞬間をキミと一緒にね
That moment together with you
MONSTERS
真っ暗な空かもしれないけど ボクらは輝きたい
It might be a pitch-black sky, but we want to shine
お目々を開いてお目々を離すなよー！
Open your eyes, and don't look away!
MONSTER イェイ！ MONSTER イェイ！ MONSTER 全人類未到の宇宙に 全速の全力で Goだ Yeah!!
MONSTER Yay! MONSTER Yay! MONSTER Into the space unknown to all humanity, with all our speed and power, Go Yeah!!
全部を欲しがれ EARTH女子！
Want it all, Earth Girls!
全速かい そうかもそうかも 宇宙のスターにスターに
Is it full power? Maybe so, maybe so. To be a star in the universe, a star
なりたい？ なりたい？
Do you want to be? Do you want to be?
なれそう？なれそうだよ！
Can we? We sure can!
キマっちゃったしね！
We totally nailed it!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制服はね無視だよ
Heave-ho in full-power mode! Just ignore the uniforms.
なんでもかんでもやっぱ 全力がいいよね
After all, everything is better when you give it your all.
笑顔はリミ（リミ） 目顔はリミ（リミ）
Smile is the limit, eye contact is the limit.
最強BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！ チェストー！
Go for the ultimate BIG BANG future! Chest-o!
手とりあったるんたった 怖くはないよね
Holding hands, tra-la-la, it's not scary, right?
夢の計測メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
The dream gauge is about to go off the charts!
地球から やってきたボクらは 本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
We, who came from Earth, are going ahead today too! Go ahead! Go ahead!
怒られるまで？
...Until we get scolded?
…怒られても止まらないのです
...Even if we get scolded, we won't stop.
最後の最後もごめんんなさーい！
Sorry until the very end!
先陣だれだい？ ボクらだい！
Who's at the vanguard? We are!
いわゆる前人ゼロの未踏地だよなあ もー１回っ！
It's a frontier where no one has gone before! One more time!
大いなる一歩さ ボクらと最高速で ういっ！
It's a giant leap, at top speed with us! Yeah!
前人ゼロの未踏地へ Go！！ そいやー！
Go to the frontier where no one has gone before!! Soiya!
よーし！次はバンドだ！できる曲を片っ端からやっていこう～！！
Alright! Next is the band! Let's play every song we can, one by one!
でもあたしたち、楽器できなくない……？
But can we even play instruments...?
こういうのはね、雰囲気っていうやつ！雰囲気が大事だから！頑張っている姿を見せれば、それでOK！
It's all about the 'vibe'! The vibe is what matters! If we just show them we're doing our best, it'll be fine!
バカにしといて結局やるのね……
You're making fun of it, but we're doing it anyway...
じゃあまず、誰が何やるのか決めよう～！ねねはギターっ！！
Then first, let's decide who's playing what! Nene is on guitar!!
じゃあししろんはドラムかな～
Then Shishiron will do drums, I guess~
ポルカは、あ、ベースで～！
Polka will be, oh, on bass~!
じゃあラミィは、シンセ、やろうかなっ
Then Lamy will... maybe do synth.
そうしたら演出も考えないとね～
Then we also need to think about the stage effects.
派手にドカーン！ってしたい！！
I want to do a big 'KABOOM'!
ざっくりだなあ～
That's pretty vague~
サビにキャノンとか出す？
Should we set off cannons during the chorus?
いいね！照明もレーザー出したりとかでピカピカにしていこう！
Nice! Let's make it flashy with lasers and lights too!
じゃあ、ねねはポルカと動き回ってパフォーマンスしよう！
Then Nene and Polka will run around and perform!
やるやる！任せてー！！
I'll do it! Leave it to me!!
だ、大丈夫か？間に合わなくてあたふたするんじゃない？
A-Are you sure? Aren't you going to panic when you can't keep up?
まあ、それもあたしたちらしさってことで～
Well, that's just part of our style~
ノリでなんとかなるなる！
We'll manage with the flow!
あ、そうだ、バンド名、どうするの？
Oh, right. What about the band name?
えー、かっこいいやつがいいなー！！
Hmm, I want something cool!!
じゃあ……青春★ピチピチフルスロットル団！！
Then... 'Youthful Bouncy Full Throttle Troupe'!!
……ださきっ！？
...Lame!?
もうちょい5期生要素も入れたいね。ラーメン、芝刈り機、低気圧……
I want to add more 5th-gen elements. Ramen, lawnmower, low pressure...
『カブトムシ』って入れたらカッコいいよ！！
It'll be cool if we add 'Beetle'!
青春低気圧★ラーメンピチピチフルスロットル芝刈り機団！！
'Youthful Low-Pressure Ramen Bouncy Full Throttle Lawnmower Troupe'!!
混ぜるな、ぐちゃぐちゃだよ……
Don't mix them together, it's a mess...
じゃあラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
Then what would you suggest, Lamy-chan?
え～、やっぱり可愛いのいいかなぁ～。『ねぽらぼハーモニー』とか♪
Hmm, I think something cute would be nice. Like 'Nepolabo Harmony'♪
それでいいのかラミィ
Are you sure about that, Lamy?
カッコよくないよラミィ
That's not cool, Lamy.
俺、恥ずかしいよラミィ
I'm embarrassed for you, Lamy.
ほんっとに……お前らっ！！
Seriously... you guys!!
よ～～し！バンド名も決まったし、やってみますかー！！
Alright! The band name is decided, so let's do this!!
これで学寮祭の注目はいただきだーっ！！
With this, we'll be the highlight of the festival!!
えっ！？あれでいくの！？
What!? We're going with that!?
いくぞー！よーい！
Here we go! Ready...
どんっ！！
Bang!!
Ready!! Steady!! Derby!!
走って 走って 憧れを越えて
Run, run, beyond our dreams
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
まだ見たことのない スピードの向こう側へ
To the other side of speed that we've never seen before
ウォームアップは完璧さ
The warm-up is perfect
地球をほら 踏み込む蹄鉄
Look, the horseshoes stepping on the Earth
ゴール前のキセキ
A miracle before the goal
仕掛ける場所は最終コーナー
The place to make our move is the final corner
あとは行けるところまで 息を切らしてたい
Then, I want to keep going as far as I can until I'm out of breath
何万と手を叩くオーディエンス
Tens of thousands of audience members clapping their hands
割れんばかり響く大歓声
Thunderous cheers echoing all around
ファンファーレが鳴る
The fanfare sounds
心音が高鳴る
My heart beats faster
動き出す秒針 夢のゲートが開く
The second hand starts moving, the gate of dreams opens
いくぞー！
Here we go!
走って！ 走って！
Run! Run!
憧れを追い越して
Surpass our dreams
次は誰の番だ！？
Whose turn is next!?
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Now, aim to be a superstar
...さあ目指すはスーパースター
...Now, aim to be a superstar!
生きてく
Live on!
ハイ!
Hi!
意味なんて
The meaning...
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
...comes after you've broken away.
勝ちたい!
I want to win!
そうこれは本能
Yes, this is instinct.
走りたい!
I want to run!
やまない衝動
An unstopping urge.
叫びたい!
I want to scream!
勝利の雄叫びよ
A war cry of victory.
轟け!
Resonate!
誰かとバチバチ競うことでしか到達し得ない輝かしいゴールライン
A brilliant finish line that can only be reached by clashing and competing.
AH どんな理屈でも言語化できない感情
AH, an emotion that no logic can put into words.
科学を超えて
Going beyond science,
カットを超えて
going beyond the cut,
熱い勝負対したいしたいしたい
I want, I want, I want to face a heated battle!
どちらが最強か
Which one is the strongest?
決めよう好敵手
Let's decide, rival.
速い者が勝つ 何も言い訳はなしだ
The fastest wins. No excuses.
よーいどん!
Ready, set, go!
飛ばして
Blast off!
ハイ!
Hi!
飛ばして
Blast off!
ハイ!
Hi!
涙さえ振り切って
Shake off even the tears.
前に足を出したんだ 悩む暇なんてない
I've stepped forward. There's no time to worry.
答えを
The answer is
ハイ!
Hi!
出すのは
given
ハイ!
Hi!
ゴールした後でも遅くない
after the finish line, it won't be too late.
GO FIGHT!
抗え本能
Resist instinct.
絶対!
Definitely!
譲れない頂上
An unyielding summit.
騒ぎたい!
I want to make some noise!
王者の雄叫びに
To the champion's roar,
続け!
follow!
Ready!
Steady!
Derby!
Ready!
Steady!
Derby!
いくぞー!
Let's go!
どんなことが起ころうたってレースが止まらないように
No matter what happens, let the race not stop.
ずっと続いてゆく この友情
This friendship will continue forever.
憎まれ口を叩いたって
Even if we exchange insults,
みんな一列になれば
when we all line up...
AH てっぺんめがけて
AH, aiming for the top,
位置についてよーい
on your mark, ready...
走って 走って
Run, run!
走って!
Run!
ハイ!
Hi!
憧れを追い越して
Overtake your aspirations.
次は誰の番だ?
Whose turn is next?
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Now, aim to be a superstar!
生きてく
Live on!
ハイ!
Hi!
意味なんて
The meaning...
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
...comes after you've broken away.
勝ちたい!
I want to win!
そうこれは本能
Yes, this is instinct.
走りたい!
I want to run!
やまない衝動
An unstopping urge.
叫びたい!
I want to scream!
勝利の雄叫びよ
A war cry of victory.
轟け!
Resonate!
Ready!
Steady!
Derby!
Ready!
Steady!
Derby!
ひゃああ〜〜〜っ！冷たーいっ！
Hyaaaa~! It's cold!
バンドして汗かいちゃったからね〜。リフレッシュ、リフレッシュ♪
We worked up a sweat during the band performance.
Refresh, refresh♪
ほら、ポルかも早く進んで〜！
Hey, Polka, move it along!
ああぁああぁ〜〜〜〜〜地獄シャワー無理〜〜〜！！！
Aaaahhhhh! I can't take this hellish shower!!!
シャワー浴びて、プールで泳いで遊んだら、きっといいアイディアも出てくるってば！
If we take a shower and play in the pool,
I'm sure we'll get some great ideas!
…そう言って、毎回遊び疲れて終わるんだけどね〜〜
You say that, but every time we just
end up getting exhausted from playing...
でもさ、夏といえばプールでしょ！ここで何かするのもアリじゃない？
But hey, summer means the pool!
Wouldn't it be cool to do something here?
プールでできることといえば……撮影会！！
Something we can do in the pool is... a photo shoot!!
ねねたちの水着姿で！
In our swimsuits!
お客さんを……悩殺♡
Seducing... the audience♡
ダメに決まってるだろ！！ 会長に怒られるよ！！
Of course not!! The president will get mad at us!!
絶対に盛り上がるのにな〜〜
It would definitely be a hit, though...
……プールにラミちゃん沈めて産地直送ラミィ水……これは売れる！！
...Sinking Lamy-chan in the pool to make 'Lamy Water
direct from the source'... This will sell!!
そこっ！ラミィから出汁をとろうとするな！ラミィ水は忘れろ！！
Hey! Stop trying to make broth out of Lamy!
Forget about the Lamy Water!!
…じゃあ、ライブしとく？プールサイドで！
...Well then, how about a live performance? On the poolside!
まぁ〜そうなるよねぇ〜！でも夏、プール、歌…最高にマッチしてるっ！
Well, I guess that's how it goes!
But summer, the pool, singing... it's the perfect match!
いいねいいね！あの夏フェスの曲やろうよ〜！水鉄砲とか持って、みんなでびしょびしょになりながら！！
Great idea! Let's do that summer festival song!
With water guns and everyone getting soaked!!
え？でもあれってエモい感じの恋愛ソングじゃなかった……？
Eh? But wasn't that a sentimental love song...?
それを私たちなりに歌い上げるってことよ！
That's why we're going to sing it in our own way!
フェスにぴったりの選曲だからね！
It's the perfect song for a festival!
それじゃあ…終わらない夏にするぞーーー！！！
In that case... let's make this an endless summer!!!
おーーー！！
Ohhh!!
君と夏フェス
作詞・作曲：宮崎朝子
Kimi to Natsu Fesu (You and the Summer Festival)
Lyrics/Composition: Miyazaki Asako
まだ照れ臭いあいつとフェスに
Going to a festival with that guy I'm still shy around
行く約束をしたはいいけど
I'm glad we made a promise to go, but
あまりノってたら引かれそう
If I get too into it, I might turn him off
控えめに楽しむって決めたんだ
I've decided to enjoy it with some restraint
でも私の大好きな
But my favorite...
ロックスター 真夏のステージで
...rock star, on the midsummer stage
スーツを着たロックスター もう
A rock star in a suit, already...
我慢できない！
I can't take it anymore!
止まらないのは私の汗
My sweat won't stop
それとも君への気持ち？
Or is it my feelings for you?
滴り落ちてく恋心
My love is dripping down
こぼれないようにすくってね
Scoop it up so it doesn't spill
止まらないのは夏への期待
My expectations for summer won't stop
忘れられない夏になるかも
It might become an unforgettable summer
夏の日差しで焼け焦げそう
I'm about to get scorched by the summer sun
すべてがスローモーションになる
Everything turns into slow motion
他人の汗もどうでもよくて
I don't even care about other people's sweat
日差しの鬱陶しさも感じない
I don't even feel the annoyance of the sunlight
でも私の大好きなロックスター
But my favorite rock star
ラストの曲終わり
At the end of the last song
ロックスター 帰ってく
The rock star leaves
ライブが終わって我に返って
The concert ends, I snap back to reality
それから… それから…
And then... and then...
ずいぶん前のほうに来ちゃってたみたい
It seems I've come quite far forward
さっきまで二人がいた場所、もう違う景色
The place where we were just a moment ago
already looks like a different scene
ああ、わたしやっちゃった 本気だったのに
Ah, I blew it, even though I was serious
うつむく私の隣に君が
Beside me as I look down, you're there
わたしの目を見つめる君 時間が止まってるみたい
You, staring into my eyes,
it's like time has stopped
少し笑って君はいう
With a slight smile, you say
「新しい君が見れたから 今日は本当に来て良かった」
"I got to see a new side of you,
so I'm really glad I came today"
照れ笑いの奥見えちゃいそうで
It seems I can see into the depths
of your shy smile
私は焦って目をそらした
I hurriedly looked away
止まらないのは二人の恋だ
What won't stop is our love
今年の夏よ
This year's summer,
終わらないでよ。
please don't end.
はあ～～～……遊んだ遊んだっ♪
Whew... we really had a blast!♪
もう、ぐったぐた…で、結局なーんも決まってないっていう(笑)
I'm wiped out... and in the end, nothing's been decided (laughs)
制服、洗濯に出しちゃったし……今日の衣装、いつもの着替えしかないよ～
I sent my uniform to the laundry... so for today's outfit,
I only have my usual clothes to change into.
もうこのままの格好で何かやるしかないねっ！
We'll just have to do something in these outfits!
でもさ、やっぱり私達にできることって…歌とダンス、かな～って思うんだよね～
But you know, I think what we can do best after all...
is singing and dancing.
うん。変に気取らずに、”いつものわたしたち”を見せるのが一番かも
Yeah. Maybe showing "our usual selves"
without putting on airs is for the best.
よしっ！じゃあ歌う曲決めようよ！！ねねは……エモい感じがいいなー。いつもと違う感じの！
Alright! Then let's decide on the songs!
As for me... I'd like something emotional. Something different from usual!
ポルカは～恋愛ソングやってみたいなぁっ♪
Polka~ wants to try a love song!♪
ラミィは元気いっぱい！合いの手たっぷりの盛り上がるやつ！！
Lamy wants something full of energy!
A hype song with lots of call-and-response!!
歌詞がグッと心に来る系の曲もいいなぁ～
Songs with lyrics that really hit you in the heart
would be nice, too...
まぁ、みんな好みがバラバラだしな〜
Well, everyone's preferences are different.
でも全部は無理くない？
But isn't doing them all impossible?
いや、できる！やってみなきゃ始まらない！
No, we can do it! It won't start if we don't try!
まさか、全部やる気？
Wait, are you planning to do them all?
もちろん！どれか一つなんてもったいないでしょ！全部やって良いのがあるか考えよう！
Of course! Picking just one would be a waste! Let's do them all and figure out which one is best!
ちょっとはお休み入れさせてね...
Let us have some breaks though...
だったらさ！各自、自分の部屋でやりたい曲をやっていこう！
In that case! Let's each perform the songs we want in our own rooms!
じゃあまずねねからねっ！この曲は〜、ねねは違う服でやる！
Then I'll start! For this song... I'm going to wear a different outfit!
わかった、やろうか〜
Understood, let's do it.
今度こそ...これで出し物を決めるぞ〜！
This time for sure... we'll decide our performance with this!
じゃあやりますか！ねね、着替え終わった？
Let's get started then! Nene, are you done changing?
オッケーッ！それじゃあ、いきま〜す！！
Okay! Well then, here I go!!
もう忘れてしまったかな　夏の木陰に座ったまま
I wonder if you've already forgotten, still sitting in the shade of summer
氷菓を口に放り込んで風を待っていた
Tossing an ice treat into our mouths, we were waiting for the wind
もう忘れてしまったかな　世の中の全部嘘だらけ
I wonder if you've already forgotten, everything in the world is full of lies
本当の価値を二人で探しに行こうと笑ったこと
How we laughed about going to find the true value together
忘れないように　色褪せないように
So that I won't forget, so that it won't fade
形に残るものが全てじゃないように
So that things that take shape aren't everything
言葉をもっと教えて
Tell me more words
夏が来るって教えて
Tell me that summer is coming
僕は描いてる
I am drawing
眼に映ったのは夏の亡霊だ
What was reflected in my eyes was a summer ghost
風にスカートが揺れて
The skirt sways in the wind
想い出なんて忘れて
Forget about things like memories
浅い呼吸をする
Taking a shallow breath
汗を拭って夏めく
Wiping away sweat, becoming like summer
もう忘れてしまったかな　夏の木陰に座った頃
I wonder if you've already forgotten, back when we sat in the shade of summer
遠くの丘から顔出した雲があったじゃないか
There was a cloud peeking out from the distant hill, wasn't there?
君はそれを掴もうとして、馬鹿みたいに空を切った手で
You tried to grab it, with your hand cutting through the air like a fool
僕は紙に雲一つを書いて、笑って握って見せて
I drew a single cloud on paper, laughed, and showed it to you in my hand
忘れないように　色褪せないように
So that I won't forget, so that it won't fade
歴史に残るものが全てじゃないから
Because things that remain in history aren't everything
今だけ顔も失くして
Just for now, lose your face too
言葉も全部忘れて
Forget all the words too
君は笑ってる
You're laughing
夏を待っている僕ら亡霊だ
We're ghosts waiting for summer
心をもっと教えて
Tell me more about your heart
夏の匂いを教えて
Tell me about the scent of summer
浅い呼吸をする
Taking a shallow breath
忘れないように　色褪せないように
So that I won't forget, so that it won't fade
心に響くものが全てじゃないから
Because things that resonate in the heart aren't everything
言葉をもっと教えて
Tell me more words
さよならだって教えて
Tell me even about goodbyes
今も見るんだよ、夏に咲いている花に亡霊を
I still see it now, the ghost in the flowers blooming in summer
言葉じゃなくて時間を
Not words, but time
時間じゃなくて心を
Not time, but the heart
浅い呼吸をする、汗を拭って夏めく
Taking a shallow breath, wiping away sweat, becoming like summer
夏の匂いがする
It smells like summer
もう忘れてしまったかな　夏の木陰に座ったまま
I wonder if you've already forgotten, still sitting in the shade of summer
氷菓を口に放り込んで風を待っていた
Tossing an ice treat into our mouths, we were waiting for the wind
I popped a popsicle in my mouth and waited for the breeze.
出会ってから付き合うまでのあの感じ
That Feeling from When We Met Until We Started Dating
土曜日は会えることが当たり前になって
Being able to see each other on Saturdays became a matter of course,
不安からのあの気持ちが消えてちょっと寂しいの
The feelings that came from anxiety have faded, and I'm a little lonely.
一生分のキスの回数すぐに超えちゃうよ
We'll quickly exceed a lifetime's worth of kisses.
まだ少し
Just a bit more,
まだもっと
even more,
特別でいたい
I want to stay special.
ずっと
Forever.
出会ってから付き合うまでのあの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling we had from when we met until we started dating.
わかってるふりなんて100年後もいらない
I won't need to pretend I understand, even 100 years from now.
二人の合図が増えたって大事なこと言おう
Even if our secret signals increase, let's say the important things.
夏の日の始まりを季節が変わっても覚えてて
Remember the beginning of that summer day, even as the seasons change.
月曜は会えないなら次の日はどう？って
If we can't meet on Monday, how about the next day?
繰り返しの言葉だってそれがもっと言ってよね
Even if it's repetitive words, please say them more.
一回だけのキスのためにすぐに会いに来た
I came to see you right away just for a single kiss.
あの時のあの場所は特別じゃないし
That place at that time wasn't special,
ずっと
Forever.
出会ってから付き合うまでのあの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling we had from when we met until we started dating.
そっけないふりなんてかっこよくもないよ
Pretending to be indifferent isn't even cool.
間違いないこと増えたって幸せちょっと違う
Even as the certainties increase, happiness is a little different.
夏の日の始まりが正しい恋よほら映してる
The beginning of that summer day is true love, look, it's being reflected.
ずっと 出会ってから付き合うまでのあの感じでいよう
Forever, let's keep that feeling we had from when we met until we started dating.
わかってるふりなんて100年後もいらない
I won't need to pretend I understand, even 100 years from now.
二人の合図が増えたって大事なこと言おう
Even if our secret signals increase, let's say the important things.
夏の日の始まりを季節が変わっても覚えてて
Remember the beginning of that summer day, even as the seasons change.
ドキッ! こういうのが恋なの?
Thump! Is This What Love is Like?
ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi, hi, hi!
ハイ
Hi!
ねえ 歌うわ そうよ あなたに
Hey, I'll sing, yes, for you.
甘えたいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
I want to be spoiled, but it might be embarrassing.
かもね
Maybe.
おい!
Hey!
願い事の呪文 ほら ムニャムニャムニャ〜
The spell for a wish, look, mumble mumble mumble~
ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi, hi, hi!
ずっとこのまま時が止まらぬかもね
Time might never stop just like this.
かもね
Maybe.
止まらぬかもね
It might not stop
かもね
Maybe
こういうのが恋なの
This is what love is
恋なのドキドキドキーン
It's love, heart thumping
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
しかもね
And also
かもね
Maybe
スキスキスキ
Love love love
昨日よりも
Even more than yesterday
かもね
Maybe
...かもね
...Maybe
かもね
Maybe
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
...かもね
...Maybe
かもね
Maybe
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ねえ歌って
Hey, sing
そうよ あなたも
That's right, you too
乙女の気持ちが
A maiden's feelings...
伝わるといいな
...I hope they reach you
いいな
How nice
のどから出そうなくらい
It's almost at the tip of my tongue
ラブラブラブ
Love love love
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ずっとこのままあなた
I want things to stay like this forever
素敵がいいな
With you being so wonderful
いいな
How nice
こういうのははじめて
This is the first time it's like this
ドキドキドキーン
Heart thumping
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ああ いいな
Ah, how nice
いいな
How nice
スキスキスキ
Love love love
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
さっきよりも
Even more than a moment ago
...いいな
...How nice
いいな
How nice
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
神様のヒマ潰し
God's Way of Killing Time
いつだって新しいことに
Always attracted to new things,
君は心奪われてから
ever since you stole my heart.
クルクルと変わって
Changing round and round,
お天気 謎だらけ
the weather is full of mysteries.
いつだってTVをつけても
Whenever I turn on the TV,
知り得たいことは1つもないよ
there's not a single thing I want to know.
似たようなウワサばかり
It's nothing but similar rumors,
謎がない
there are no mysteries.
手に入れたいんだ 君の心の地図
I want to get my hands on the map of your heart.
Ah 探し当てたい 宝物の在り処
Ah, I want to find the location of the treasure.
その心の奥を掴んで
Gripping deep into that heart,
揺さぶるものは何？
what is it that shakes it?
考えてるだけで日が暮れて
Just thinking about it, the day ends.
苦しくて 切なくて 楽しくて
Painful, suffocating, and fun,
日が暮れる
the day ends.
勘ぐってありえない想像
Prying into impossible imaginations,
へこんだかと思えば笑ったり
feeling down then laughing the next moment.
あたしはあたしで相当
In my own way, I am quite
謎だらけ
full of mysteries.
ハマってしまったら 恋は迷路
Once you fall for it, love is a maze.
Ah 角を曲がれば 行き止まりばかり
Ah, turn the corner and it's nothing but dead ends.
物語の鍵を握って
Holding the key to the story,
遊んでいるのは誰？
who is the one playing?
ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
A quite distasteful way to kill time.
退屈を弄ぶ 神様のヒマ潰し
Toying with boredom, it's God's way of killing time.
ヒマ潰し
Killing time.
このところの
Lately...
不安な夜は
During anxious nights,
胸の奥の
Deep in my chest,
胸の奥の奥
Deep, deep in my chest,
チリチリと鳴き通す
A prickling sound cries through.
Ah 会えない理由はわかってるのに
Ah, even though I know the reason we can't meet,
物語の鍵を握って 遊んでいるのは誰？
Who is it that holds the key to the story and plays around?
ずいぶん悪趣味な暇潰し
It's a quite distasteful way to kill time.
その心の奥を掴んで 揺さぶるものは何？
What is it that grabs the depths of that heart and shakes it?
考えてるだけで日が暮れて
The day ends just from me thinking about it,
苦しくて 切なくて 楽しくて 日が暮れて
Painful, heartbreaking, and joyful, the day ends,
苦しくて 切なくて この恋に明け暮れる
Painful, heartbreaking, I spend all my time in this love.
つっ……疲れた～～！！
Phew... I'm tired!!
さすがに……全員連続は応えたね……
As expected... doing everyone back-to-back was tough...
でもでもっ！どの曲もサイコーだった～～っ♪
But, but! Every song was the absolute best!
うん…、でも、“わたしたちらしさ”があるかって言われると…ちょっと悩むな～
Yeah... but if you asked if it felt like 'us'... I'm a bit unsure.
まもなく、学寮祭が始まります
The dormitory festival will begin shortly.
関係する生徒の皆さんは、速やかに準備をお願いします
Students involved, please begin your preparations promptly.
やっ、やば～い！！もう始まっちゃうってば～～っ！
Oh no! It's starting already!
え～～お腹空いた～～ ちょっと購買行ってくるねっ！！
Ugh, I'm hungry. I'm gonna go to the shop for a bit!
じゃ、わたしも行く～～♪
Then I'll go too.
ラミィも行く～～！
Lamy's going too!
えぇ～～っ！？ちょっと～！？
Wait, what?! Hold on!
パン残ってるかな～～
I wonder if there's any bread left...
……ん？あれって……なんだ？？
...Hm? What is... that??
こ、これは
Th-this is...
もしかして……！
Could it be...!
もしかなくても！
No doubt about it!
間違いないっ！！
It's definitely it!!
ねぽらぼアニバーサリーパレード！！
NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade!!
ねぽらぼ5周年グッズがこんなところに！
NePoLaBo 5th Anniversary goods are in a place like this!
きっと今日の配信終わりに出るやつだ！
This is definitely the stuff that drops after today's stream ends!
気になる～
I'm so curious!
これは順番に見ていくしかないでしょ！
We've got no choice but to look through them one by one!
まずは、プレミアムアクリル色紙！
First up, the Premium Acrylic Shikishi!
今回のグッズのテーマが、花鳥風月！
The theme for these goods is 'Kacho Fugetsu' (Beauties of Nature)!
七原しえさんが描いてくれました！ ねねたちの和服姿、綺麗でしょ！
Shie Nanahara drew this for us! Our kimono outfits look beautiful, right!
アクリル色紙には、ねねたちの複製サインと、ロゴが入っています！
The acrylic shikishi features our reproduced signatures and the logo!
アクリルの脚もついてるから、机に飾っておくこともできるよ！
It also comes with acrylic legs, so you can display it on your desk!
めっちゃ可愛いので、ぜひ！
It's super cute, so please check it out!
次！
Next!
続いては、オフィシャルホロカスリーブ アニバーサリーパレードねぽらぼバージョン！
Next is the Official Holoca Sleeves: Anniversary Parade NePoLaBo Version!
もちろん、ホロカが入るスリーブです！
Of course, these are sleeves designed to fit Holoca cards!
1パック60枚入ってるから、これでねぽらぼデッキを作り上げてください！
One pack has 60 sleeves, so please build a NePoLaBo deck with these!
いや、もう最近はね、ねぽらぼ全員出ちゃいましたから
Well, recently, all of NePoLaBo have been released in the card game!
もうこれでお前のオリジナルの、デッキ構築をして、優勝していくんだ！
So build your original deck with these and aim for the win!
さあ、お前ならできる！やるしかない！
Come on, you can do it! You've got to do it!
見ているお前ら、ねぽらぼリスナー、お前ら頑張ってくれ！
All of you watching, NePoLaBo listeners, give it your best!
次！
Next!
続いては、アクリルスタンド！
Next up, Acrylic Stands!
プレミアムアクリル色紙とは別の表情をした、ラミィたちのアクリルスタンドです！
These are acrylic stands of Lamy and the others with different expressions!
花鳥風月で、花・春が桃鈴ねね
Based on 'Kacho Fugetsu', Flower/Spring is Momosuzu Nene,
鳥・秋が獅白ぼたん
Bird/Autumn is Shishiro Botan,
風・夏が尾丸ポルカ
Wind/Summer is Omaru Polka,
月・冬が雪花ラミィとなっています！
and Moon/Winter is Yukihana Lamy!
では、次！
Now, next!
最後は、記念メダル！専用のケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルです！
Last is the Memorial Medal! It comes with a special case and drawstring bag!
それぞれタレントカラーと名前が入っていて、期生ごとにデザインが違うので、コレクションアイテムとしてぜひ揃えてみてください！
Each features a talent's color and name with generation-specific designs, so try collecting them all!
以上、ねぽらぼアニバーサリーパレードのグッズでした！
That's all for the NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade merchandise!
わあー！イエーイ！よろしくお願いします！ねー！
Waaa! Yay! Please take care of us! Right!
それでは──これより、学寮祭を開始いたします
Well then... the Dorm Festival will now begin.
ご来場の皆様、どうぞ最後までお楽しみください
To all our visitors, please enjoy until the very end.
やばい学寮祭始まるって！
Oh no, the Dorm Festival is starting!
ねねたちも行かなきゃ！
We have to go too!
結局、何も買えなかったんだけど！
We ended up not buying anything though!
しゃーなし。戻って学寮祭の話しますか…
Can't be helped. Shall we go back and talk about the festival?
ででこれは…何をしているの？？
So, um... what are we doing??
ねねたちには、歌とダンスしかない！！ならばギリギリまで、全力で練習するしかないでしょー！！
All we have is singing and dancing!! So we have no choice but to practice with all our might until the last second!!
もうお客さん入っているけどね(笑)
But the audience is already inside (laughs)
あああ、もうやるしかない！！
Ah, geez, we just have to do it!!
でもさ、肝心の何やるかを決めてないのでは？
But wait, haven't we decided on the most important thing: what we're going to do?
(…………)
(Thinking...)
……でさ、お客さんたちも見たいのってやっぱり私たちらしさだよね
But you know, what the audience wants to see is... well, something that's "us," right?
それなら…オリ曲じゃない？
In that case... wouldn't it be our original songs?
じゃあ、全部やろう！！
Then, let's do all of them!!
またぁ～～～！？
Again!?
1つじゃダメダメっ！衣装もぜーいん着替えて、たくさん歌おうよ！！
Just one isn't enough! Let's change into all our costumes and sing lots of songs!!
メドレーってこと！？いいじゃんそれ！！
You mean a medley!? Oh, that sounds great!!
あぁ～～、いいかも。
Ah~~, that might be good.
で、順番はどうするの？？
And what about the order??
そんなんパッションでどうにかなるなるっ！！
Something like that will work out with passion!!
こりゃ大変なことになりそうですね。
This looks like it's going to be quite an ordeal.
う～～ん……
Ummm...
ししろん？どうしたの？？
Shishiron? What's wrong??
いや、何か忘れている気がするんだけど……思い出せない。
No, I feel like I'm forgetting something... but I can't remember.
大丈夫大丈夫っ！これを歌えば学寮祭は、ねねたちのものっ！！
It's okay, it's okay! If we sing this, the Dorm Festival will be ours!!
よっしゃいくぞー！！
Alright, let's go!!
私たちらしさ見せるよ！
We'll show them our true colors!
うんっ、とりあえず、やるだけやろう！せーのっ！
Yeah, for now, let's just do what we can! One, two!
ねぽらぼメドレー！！
Nepolabo Medley!!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
The light shines on our future
始めようか さあ Diving
Shall we begin, now diving
待っても意味ない Timing
No point in waiting, timing
でもたまに止まって Thinking Thinking
But sometimes stop and think, thinking
変えてみせる Change
I'll show I can change it, change
踏み出すのさ Stepping
Step forward, stepping
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ My Dream
I'll show I can grab it, my sparkling dream
叶う日まで Story 繋ぐから
Until the day it comes true, I'll connect the story
だって君に ずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to watch me forever
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, together everybody
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
The light shines on our future
Hyper Jumpin' Now
Hyper Jumpin'
子供くらい はしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
It's better to frolic around like a child
低気圧から 追い上がっていくテンション
Tension rising from the low pressure
このままスピード加速して
Just like this, accelerate the speed
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the end
止まらない気持ちは 助走つけて
Accelerating the feelings that won't stop
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin', let's leap
ハイになって灰になるまで Dash and Shake it up
Get high until you're ash, dash and shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Woh... ドキドキしたい Gimmie Gimmie Gimmie 愛
Woh... I want my heart to race, gimmie gimmie gimmie love
Wohoo... もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
Wohoo... I want to jump higher and higher
This is No No 好きなら More More More
This is no no, if you like it more, more, more
邪魔するノイズは 打ち消せ Bang Bang Bang
Cancel out the distracting noise, bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ アンチは無視して
I just want to play, ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして 蹴っ飛ばせ Kick it!
Laugh it off and kick it away! Kick it!
Jump Around!!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
Cosmic Wonderful Tour!
一歩目が すでに異空間
Our first step is already in a different dimension
キラリ 渦に巻き込まれた？
Sparkling, were you sucked into the vortex?
違うよ 出会いたくって
No, it's because I wanted to meet you
ホラ みんなここにいる
See? Everyone is right here
夢のようで だけどね
It feels like a dream, yet
ファンタジーじゃない感
it's not quite a fantasy
流星群 負けないよう
Outshining the meteor shower,
光放って！
let the light burst forth!
どんな憧れも飛び越えて
Surpassing any yearning
銀河のまん中 行進しよう
Let's march into the center of the galaxy
きらめきのシンフォニーさ
It's a symphony of sparkles
足跡だって 星になる
Even our footprints will become stars
1, 2, 3... Yeah! 奇跡 散りばめよう
1, 2, 3... Yeah! Let's scatter miracles
1, 2, 3... Yeah! 何万光年を
1, 2, 3... Yeah! Over tens of thousands of light-years
1, 2, 3... Yeah! 旅してゆく 季節が今
1, 2, 3... Yeah! The season of our journey
始まったんだよきっと！
has surely begun right now!
せーの！
One, two!
Wonderful Tour!
君に届け 星のメロディー
May the starry melody reach you
想いをギュッギュッと詰め込んで
Packed tight with all our feelings
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony I'm playing with you
これからも ずっと続いていく
will continue on forever
Twinkle 4 You
ねえねえ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come a little closer
回り始めた世界で 踊らない？ 終わらない
In this world that's started turning, won't you dance? It'll never end
わくわく 魔法かけたら
When the excitement casts a spell
ドキドキはSyncして ほら Party Time 止まらない
Our heartbeats sync up, look, it's Party Time and it won't stop
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
With a wish in our hearts
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で歌いましょう
Let's sing in the night sky
君に響け 星のメロディー
May the starry melody resonate with you
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony I'm playing with you
これからも ずっと続いていく
will continue on forever
Twinkle 4 You
君に響け 星のメロディー
May the starry melody resonate with you
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と繋がっている この宇宙に
In this sky that connects us
宝石を 散りばめよう
Let's scatter jewels
君に届け 星のメロディー
May the starry melody reach you
想いをギュッギュッと詰め込んで
Packed tight with all our feelings
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony I'm playing with you
これからも ずっと続いていく
will continue on forever
La La La...
やっぱ ねぽらぼ だな〜！！
It's NePoLaBo after all!!
これで学寮祭は、大成功〜！
With this, the Dormitory Festival is a huge success!!
あ〜……
Ah...
えっ、ししろん？ どうしたの？
Eh, Shishiron? What's wrong?
いやさ…… 確かに良かったんだけど…… なんかこう…… 「何か」を忘れてる気がするんだよね
No, it's just that, it was definitely great, but... somehow... I feel like we're forgetting something.
なぁに言ってんの！？ このメドレーで完璧だってば！
What are you talking about?! This medley made it perfect!
そうだよ〜！ これでみんな、ひとつになってハッピー！
Exactly! Everyone's united now and happy!!
来てくれた人たちも、きっと、ラミィたちの声を聞いて、喜んでくれたよ！
The people who came must have been happy hearing our voices too!
ひとつ…… 声…… あっ！！
United... voices... Ah!!!
私たち、新曲作ってたじゃん！！
We made a new song, didn't we!!
あっ……
Ah...
わすれてたぁーーーーー！！！
I totally forgot!!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのにっ！！
And we practiced so hard for it!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのに〜っ！！
We practiced so much!!
作ったのはいいけど……「出すタイミングどうしよう」って言ってたら、
We made it, but while we were saying, "When should we bring it out?"
完全に忘れてた……
I completely forgot...
出すタイミング絶対にここだったな〜
The timing to bring it out was definitely right here.
もうステージ真っ暗だし〜〜〜！
The stage is already dark!
……お客さん、まだいてくれてる、かな……
I wonder if the audience... is still there for us...
……大丈夫！
It's okay!
今なら、まだ……ギリギリ間に合う！！
We can still... just barely make it now!!
ねぇ、そこの君！！まだ……見ててくれるよね？
Hey, you there! You're still... watching, right?
ねねたちの、新しい曲──聞いてくれる？
Will you listen to... our new song?
うん、うん……きっと、聞いてくれるって信じてる！
Yeah, yeah... I'm sure they'll listen, I believe it!
最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's get hyped together until the very end!
それでは──改めて……んっん……
Well then—once again... *ahem*...
聞いてください──ねぽらぼの新曲です
Please listen to it—Nepolabo's new song.
この先、みんなとなら、どこまでも行けると願って──歌います
With the hope that we can go anywhere with everyone from now on... we sing.
5周年──その先の未来もずっと一緒に見守り……歩んでください
5th Anniversary—please continue to watch over us and walk with us into the future.
1人じゃ辿り着けない場所へ……みんなで──
To the place we can't reach alone... all together—
ひとつになる声
Voices becoming one.
暗闇の中で 見つけた声
A voice found in the darkness
そのしるべを 辿りながら
Following that signpost
僕らは
We...
走るよ
Are running
ひとつになる声
歌：ねぽらぼ
作詞・作曲・編曲：中野領太
Voices Becoming One
Song by: Nepolabo
Lyrics, Music & Arrangement: Ryota Nakano
ひとりぼっちだった日
Days when I was all alone
先見えなかった日
Days when I couldn't see ahead
だけど君と出会えて
But after meeting you
そっと 扉を開けた
I gently opened the door
手のひらの中に また1を足して
Adding another '1' into my palm
何度も 奇跡を叶えよう
Let's make miracles happen over and over
澄み渡る空の彼方
Beyond the crystal clear sky
太陽と踊る 羽になる
Becoming wings that dance with the sun
情熱が突き動かす
Passion drives us
僕らの明日を
Our tomorrow
照らして
Illuminate it
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは 強く心を結んで
Running towards the same dream, we bind our hearts strongly
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
To the end of the world, we can go anywhere
これからまた続いていく道 1人じゃ辿り着けない
The road that continues from now on, I can't reach it alone
だから この背中預けるよ
So, I'll entrust my back to you
信じている 君の手を
I believe in your hand
僕らの未来を
Our future
みんなの声を
Everyone's voice
君らしいって思う その積み重ねが
I think it's just like you, those accumulations
なぜか嬉しくなるの
Somehow make me happy
きっとこれからもそう
Surely it'll be that way from now on too
手のひらの中の 大切な日々が
The precious days in my palm
たくさんの光を奏でて
Playing so much light
君と笑った
I laughed with you
始まりの時の願い
The wish from when it started
今もほら輝いてる
Look, it's still shining now
未来まで連れてゆこう
Let's take it with us to the future
暗闇を抜けた先に
At the end of the darkness
みんなの笑顔
Everyone's smiles
見つけた
I found them
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは 強く心を結んで
Running towards the same dream, we bind our hearts strongly
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
To the end of the world, we can go anywhere
これからまた続いていく道 1人じゃ辿り着けない
The road that continues from now on, I can't reach it alone
だから この背中預けるよ
So, I'll entrust my back to you
信じている 君の手を
I believe in your hand
僕らの未来を
Our future
みんなの声を
Everyone's voice
ひとつに
Becoming one
みんなの声を
Everyone's voice
重ねて
Overlapping
ひとつに
As one
重ねて
Together
みんなの声を
All of our voices
ひとつに
As one
みんなの声を
All of our voices
重ねて
Together
みんなの声を
All of our voices
ひとつに
As one
心合わせて
With our hearts in sync
重ねて
Together
僕らは願う
We make a wish
ひとつに
As one
光の中で
Within the light
重ねて
Together
ひとつになる声
Voices becoming one
＜出演＞
桃鈴ねね / 雪花ラミィ / 尾丸ポルカ / 獅白ぼたん
Momosuzu Nene / Yukihana Lamy / Omaru Polka / Shishiro Botan
ねぽらぼ学園 ☆5周年記念！！輝く学寮祭☆
NePoLaBo Academy ☆5th Anniversary!! Shining Dormitory Festival☆